A Guide to the Virginia Academy of Science Records, 1920-2005
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Box 5, 1953-1969 (Box 5)
  - Visiting Scientist Program--Correspondence, 1959-1960
  - Reports on Examination, 1960-1963
  - Financial Statement--Report--J. Waddell Rison & Co. and First & Merchant National Bank, 1960
  - Council--Minutes, 1960-1969
- Box 6, 1960-1964 (Box 6)
  - Officers and Committees, 1960-1961
  - Council--Minutes, 1960-1961
  - Committee Reports, 1960-1961
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence--L. I. Miller, 1960-1961
  - Finance and Endowment Committee--Correspondence, 1960-1961
  - Geology Section--Correspondence--F. W. Trainer, 1960-1961
  - Isabel Boggs--Correspondence--VAS History, 1960-1961
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence, 1960-1961
  - Research Committee--Correspondence, 1960-1961
  - Officers, Members of Council, and Committee members, 1960-1973
  - Financial Statement--Report--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1961
  - Academy Assembly and Council, 1961
  - Officers and Committees, 1961-1962
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Annual Meeting, Membership, and Virginia Journal of Science, 1961-1962
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence--T. Graham Copeland, 1961-1962
  - Council--Minutes, 1961-1962
  - Geology Section--Correspondence, 1961-1962
  - Isabel Boggs--Correspondence--Jeffers and VAS History, 1961-1962
  - VAS History, 1926-1962--Draft Ms--George W. Jeffers, 1961-1962
  - History of Early Publications of the Virginia Academy of Science--Harshbarger, 1961-1962
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence--Jeffers, 1961-1962
  - Research Committee--Correspondence, 1961-1962
  - Science Education Committee--Correspondence--Jeffers, 1961-1962
  - Virginia Journal of Science--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1961-1962
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1961-1968
  - Financial Statement--Report--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1962
  - Officers and Committees, 1962-1963
  - Russell J. Rowlett, Jr.--Correspondence--Secretary, 1962-1963
  - J. J. Taylor--Correspondence--Committee reports to the president, 1962-1963
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence--Edward A. Bouchers, 1962-1963
  - Awards Committee--Report, 1962-1963
  - By-laws and Constitution, 1962-1963
  - Council--Minutes, 1962-1963
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1962-1963
  - Geology Section--Correspondence, 1962-1963
  - G. W. Jeffers--Correspondence--VAS history; Isabel Boggs, 1962-1963
  - Files from President Bill Wilson, 1962-1963, 1977-1978
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1962-1970
  - Taxes and reports to the IRS, 1962-1970
  - Financial Statement--Reports--J. Waddell Rison & Co. and First & Merchants National Bank, 1963
  - R. J. Rowlett, Jr.--Correspondence--Secretary, 1963-1964
  - Officers and Committees, 1963-1964
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence, 1963-1964
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence, 1963-1964
  - By-laws and Constitution, 1963-1964
  - Council-Minutes, 1963-1964
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1963-1964
  - Geology Section--Correspondence--Robert L. Ellison, 1963-1964
  - VAS History--Correspondence and reports--Jeffers and Boggs, 1963-1964
  - VAS History--Correspondence, reports, and Ms drafts--Astronomy, Mathematics, and Physics Section, Bacteriology Section, Chemistry Section, Education Section, Engineering Section, Geology Section, Medical Sciences Section, Psychology Section, Research Committee, Science Teachers Section, Statistics Section, Virginia Institute for Scientific Research, and Virginia Journal of Science, 1963-1964
  - Long Range Planning--Correspondence, 1963-1964
  - Long Range Planning--Correspondence, 1963-1964
  - Research Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1963-1964
- Box 7, 1963-1966 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Symposium on Human Resources--Correspondence and speakers--Roscoe D. Hughes, 1963-1964
  - Files from Senator Lloyd Bird, 1963-1964
  - Miscellaneous files, 1963-1965
  - Financial Statement--Reports--J. Waddell Rison & Co. and First & Merchants National Bank, 1964
  - Officers and Committees, 1964-1965
  - Obenshain and Hughes--Correspondence--Presidents, 1964-1965
  - R. J. Rowlett, Jr.--Correspondence--Secretary, 1964-1965
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Natural Resources Committee, Negus Lectureship, Science Foundation, and Virginia Flora, 1964-1965
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Correspondence--Chemistry, Engineering, Geology, and Physics, 1964-1965
  - Agricultural Science Committee--Correspondence and Minutes--T. J. Marlowe, 1964-1965
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science--Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - Awards--Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - Council--Minutes, 1964-1965
  - M. B. Rowe--Correspondence--Council and Local Arrangements, 1964-1965
  - By-laws and Constitution--Revision, 1964-1965
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1964-1965
  - VAS History--Correspondence--I. Boggs, 1964-1965
  - Virginia Symposium on Human Resources--Correspondence about publication, 1964-1965
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Grant and Virginia Journal of Science--Correspondence and Financial Reports, 1964-1965
  - Research Committee-Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - Resolutions Committee--Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - Virginia Journal of Science--Correspondence--R. D. Hughes, 1964-1965
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Correspondence, 1964-1965
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1964-1966
  - Finance Committee, 1964-1968
  - Financial Statement--Report--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1965
  - NSF Grant--Statement--M. Rowe, 1965
  - Officers and Committees, 1965-1966
  - R. C. Berry--Correspondence--Secretary, 1965-1966
  - R. D. Hughes--Correspondence--President, 1965-1966
  - S. S. Obenshain--Correspondence--Immediate past-president, 1965-1966
  - R. L. Rowlett, Jr.--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Stanley B. Williams--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - By-laws and Constitution--Includes revisions, 1965-1966
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Awards Committee, Flora Committee, Nominations Committee, Place of Meeting Committee, and Resolutions Committee, 1965-1966
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Correspondence--Astronomy, Mathematics, and Physics, Materials Science, and Space Science and Technology, 1965-1966
  - Advisory Committees--Correspondence--Business Advisory Committee and Museum Advisory Committee, 1965-1966
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence, 1965-1966
- Box 8, 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence--Rowe, 1965-1966
  - Awards and Research Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1965-1966
  - Biologists of Virginia--Biographical sketches, 1965-1966
  - By-laws and Constitution, 1965-1966
  - Council--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Council--Minutes, Agenda, and President’s Dinner--Hughes, president, 1965-1966
  - Council--Minutes, 1965-1966
  - Education--Correspondence--Science Education Committee, Advisory Committee on Educational TV, and Science Talent Search, 1965-1966
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1965-1966
  - Financial and Budget Records, 1965-1966
  - Treasurer's Report--Rowe, 1965-1966
  - History Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Local Arrangements Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1965-1966
  - Local Range Planning Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Membership Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1965-1966
  - Institutional Memberships--Correspondence--Rommer and Sanger, 1965-1966
  - Natural Resources Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence-Hughes, 1965-1966
  - Research Committee--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Virginia Journal of Science--Correspondence--Hughes, 1965-1966
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Budget--National Science Foundation Grant, 1965-1966
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Correspondence, 1965-1966
  - Budgets, 1965-1966
  - History of the Virginia Academy of Science. 1923-1945--Thesis--Harry J. Staggers, 1966
  - Financial Statement--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1966
  - Budget Statements--Rowe and Berry, 1966
  - Financial Statements--Social Security Tax--Visiting Scientists Program, 1966
  - Financial Statements--NSF Grant--Rowe, 1966
  - Report on Duties of Officers, 1966
  - Budget Proposal, 1966
  - Secretary's Correspondence, 1966
  - Officers and Committees, 1966-1967
  - Roscoe D. Hughes, President--Correspondence--Williams and Cole Obenshain, 1966-1967
  - Maurice B. Rowe--Correspondence--Executive Secretary and Treasurer, 1966-1967
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--AAAS/ Academy Conference, Business Advisory Committee, Educational TV Committee, History Committee, Local Arrangements Committee, Membership Committee, and Natural Resources Committee, 1966-1967
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence and Minutes--A. T. Hart, 1966-1967
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence--D. Rae Carpenter, 1966-1967
  - Annual Meeting --Correspondence, Speech, and Reports--R. D. Hughes, 1966-1967
  - Collegiate Chapters--Correspondence, 1966-1967
  - Constitution, 1966-1967
  - Council and Executive Committee--Correspondence, 1966-1967
  - Finance and Budget--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1966-1967
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence--Turner, 1966-1967
  - Membership Drive--Correspondence--Hughes, 1966-1967
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1966-1967
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Seigel and Carpenter, 1966-1967
  - Research Committee--Correspondence, 1966-1967
- Box 9, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - Publications Committee, 1966-1967
  - Resolutions Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1966-1967
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Correspondence, Reports, and Accounts--Hughes and Rowe, 1966-1967
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Requests for Reimbursement of Expenditures, 1966-1967
  - Financial Statements--Rowe, 1966-1967
  - Research Committee, 1966-1969
  - Publications Committee, 1966-1974
  - Bank books, 1966-1979
  - Financial Statements--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1967
  - Financial Statements--VAS--Rowe, 1967
  - NSF Grant--Statements--Rowe, 1967
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Financial Records--Social Security Tax, 1967
  - Virginia Museum of Science, 1967
  - Budget, 1967
  - Constitution, 1967-1968
  - Officers and Committees, 1967-1968
  - Rodney C. Berry--Correspondence--Executive Secretary and Treasurer, 1967-1968
  - M. Rowe--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Paul B. Siegel--Correspondence--president-elect, 1967-1968
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Collegiate Chapters Committee, Place of Meeting Committee, Resolutions Committee, and Science Talent Search Committee, 1967-1968
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Appointment of Registered Agent--Correspondence--Rowe, 1967-1968
  - Astronomy, Mathematics, and Physics Section--Correspondence and Abstracts--Turner, 1967-1968
  - Council--Correspondence and Minutes, 1967-1968
  - Dismal Swamp--Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1968
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1968
  - NSF Grant--Correspondence and Budget--Rowe, 1967-1968
  - NSF Grant--Bank Statements--#GW 1096, 1967-1968
  - History of Science Committee--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Medical Science Section--Minutes, 1967-1968
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1967-1968
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory--Dismal Swamp, 1967-1968
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Carpenter--Dismal Swamp, 1967-1968
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Tax Exemption Study--Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Virginia Museum of Science--Correspondence--Carpenter, 1967-1968
  - Visiting Scientists Program and Virginia Junior Academy of Science--Reports and Financial statements--Rowe and I. D. Wilson, 1967-1968
  - Fundraising Committee, 1967-1968
  - Budget Proposal, 1967-1968
  - Virginia Junior Academy of Science, 1967-1969
  - Place of Meeting Committee, 1967-1969
  - Grants from the National Science Foundation, 1967, 1969, 1975, 1976
  - Financial Statement--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1968
  - Treasurer’s Report, 1968
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Financial Records--Social Security Tax, 1968
  - Lexington Council, 1968
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1968
  - Fiscal Reports, 1968
- Box 10, 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - Officers and Committees, 1968-1969
  - Duties of officers and committees, 1968-1969
  - R. C. Berry--Correspondence--Executive Secretary/Treasurer, 1968-1969
  - E. F. Turner, Jr.--Correspondence, 1968-1969
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Assembly Committee, Business Advisory Committee, History Committee, Publications Committee, Resolutions Committee, and Trustees Committee, 1968-1969
  - Miscellaneous Sections Correspondence--Astronomy, Math, & Physics, Materials Science, Psychology, Space Science & Technology, and Engineering, 1968-1969
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence, 1968-1969
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence--Rowe, 1968-1969
  - Awards Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1968-1969
  - Council--Correspondence--Rowe (minutes), 1968-1969
  - Council--Minutes--June/October 1968 and January/March 1969, 1968-1969
  - Council--Minutes--May 1969, 1968-1969
  - Article of Incorporation--Amendment--Photocopy of 1927 certificate, 1968-1969
  - Executive Committee--Correspondence and Minutes--Siegel, President, 1968-1969
  - Executive Committee--Minutes, 1968-1969
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence-Harshbarger, 1968-1969
  - Finances, budgets, and expenses, 1968-1969
  - Flora Committee--Correspondence--A. M. Harvill, Jr., 1968-1969
  - Fund Raising--Correspondence--Hughes, 1968-1969
  - Local Arrangements Committee--Correspondence--Carpenter, 1968-1969
  - Long Range Planning/Publications Committee--Correspondence--Turner, 1968-1969
  - Membership Committee--Correspondence, 1968-1969
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory, Dismal Swamp, 1968-1969
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Carpenter, Dismal Swamp, 1968-1969
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1968-1969
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory--History of VAS chapters 4-6 (1946-1966), 1968-1969
  - Science Talents Search Committee--Correspondence, 1968-1969
  - Treasurer’s Report--Correspondence--Rowe, 1968-1969
  - Virginia Museum of Science--Correspondence--Turner, 1968-1969
  - D. Rae Carpenter--Correspondence, 1968-1970
  - Finance and Quarter reports, 1968-1983
  - Financial Statements--J. Waddell Rison & Co., 1969
  - Financial Statements--Correspondence--Rowe, 1969
  - Registered Agent--Correspondence--Rowe, 1969
  - VAS Museum Fund, 1969
  - Executive Committee--Minutes, 1969
  - Budget, 1969
  - Creation of Executive Secretary-Treasurer, 1969
  - Budget Finance Committee, 1969
  - Conferences and VAS supported programs, 1969
  - VAS program at Virginia Military Institute, 1969
  - 47th Annual Meeting, May 7-10, 1969
  - Living Past Presidents, 1969-1970
  - By-laws and Constitution--Officers, 1969-1970
  - R. C. Berry--Correspondence--Executive Secretary-Treasurer, 1969-1970
  - D. R. Carpenter--Correspondence, 1969-1970
  - Turner--Correspondence, 1969-1970
  - Miscellaneous Committee--Reports--Academy Conference, Business Advisory, Collegiate Chapters, Flora, Long Range Planning, Membership, Museum of Science, Nominations, Publications, Research, Trustees, Virginia Junior Academy of Science, and Visiting Scientists Program, 1969-1970
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Agricultural Science, Astronomy, Math, & Physics, Botany, Chemistry, Geology, and Medical Sciences, 1969-1970
- Box 11, 1969-1971 (Box 11)
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence and Minutes, 1969-1970
  - Annual Meeting --Correspondence--Carpenter, 1969-1970
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1969-1970
  - Local Arrangements Committee--Correspondence--Rowe and Burke, 1969-1970
  - Local Arrangements Committee--Summary Report, 1969-1970
  - Officers and Committees, 1969-1970
  - Awards Committee, 1969-1970
  - Committee Appointments--Correspondence--Carpenter, President, 1969-1970
  - Council--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1969-1970
  - Council--Correspondence--Turner, 1969-1970
  - Council--Minutes, 1969-1970
  - Executive Committee--Correspondence--Ad Hoc Committee, 1969-1970
  - Executive Committee--Correspondence and minutes--October/September 1969, 1969-1970
  - Executive Committee--Correspondence and minutes--March 1970, 1969-1970
  - Executive Committee--Correspondence and minutes--February 1970, 1969-1970
  - Finance Committee--Reports and budget--Harshbarger, 1969-1970
  - Financial Statements--NSF Grant GW 4229 and Virginia Junior Academy Project, 1969-1970
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence and report--Harshbarger, 1969-1970
  - Flora Committee--Correspondence--Rowe, 1969-1970
  - Local Arrangements Committee--Correspondence--Carpenter, 1969-1970
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence--Turner, 1969-1970
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence--Dale D. Ulrich, 1969-1970
  - Nominations Committee--Correspondence, 1969-1970
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory, Dismal Swamp, 1969-1970
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Carpenter, Dismal Swamp, 1969-1970
  - Sections--Correspondence--Ad Hoc Committee on Restructuring of Sections, 1969-1970
  - Science Talent Search Committee--Correspondence, 1969-1970
  - Virginia Museum of Science--Correspondence--Remsburg, 1969-1970
  - Virginia Museum of Science--Correspondence--Rowe and Turner, 1969-1970
  - Report of the Virginia Museum of Science Study Commission, 1969-1970
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Report, 1969-1970
  - Constitution and By-laws, 1969-1970
  - Proposed Botany Section, 1969-1970
  - Membership, 1969-1971
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1972
  - Financial Statements--J. Waddell Rison & Co., includes Treasurer’s Report, 1970
  - Academy Conference, 1926-1970--C. L. Baker, 1970
  - Appointment of Registered Agent--Correspondence--Rowe, 1970
  - Douglas paper, 1970
  - Miscellaneous files, 1970
  - Revisions of VAS constitution and by-laws, 1970
  - Mailing list changes, 1970
  - Social Security Tax Refund, 1970
  - R. C. Berry--Correspondence--Executive Secretary-Treasurer, 1970-1971
  - M. B. Rowe--Correspondence--President, 1970-1971
  - E. F. Turner, Jr.--Correspondence--President-elect, 1970-1971
  - Officers and Committees, 1970-1971
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Board of Trustees, Business Advisory Committee, Membership Committee, Resolutions Committee, Virginia Journal of Science, 1970-1971
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Correspondence--Psychology, Astronomy, Math & Physics, Biology, Botany, Chemistry, Engineering, Geology, and Medical Sciences, 1970-1971
  - Agricultural Science--Correspondence and minutes--M. W. Alexander, 1970-1971
  - Annual Meeting and Local Arrangements Program--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1970-1971
  - Annual Meeting--Correspondence--Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Local Arrangements Program and Banquet--Correspondence--Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Annual Meeting--Schedule of Responsibilities, 1970-1971
  - Awards Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1970-1971
- Box 12, 1970-1973 (Box 12)
  - Academy Conference--Minutes, 1970-1971
  - By-laws and Constitution, 1970-1971
  - Conservation Committee--Correspondence--Jeffers and Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Council and Executive Committee--Correspondence and minutes, 1970-1971
  - Council--Correspondence and minutes--Fall 1970, Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Council--Correspondence and minutes--February 1970, Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Council--Correspondence and minutes--March 1970, Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Executive Committee--Minutes, 1970-1971
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1970-1971
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Financial Statements--NSF Grant WO 05886 and Virginia Junior Academy of Science, 1970-1971
  - Flora Committee--Correspondence, 1970-1971
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence and reports, 1970-1971
  - Nominations Committee--Correspondence, 1970-1971
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory, Rowe, and Dismal Swamp, 1970-1971
  - Science Talent Search--Report, 1970-1971
  - Virginia Museum of Science--Correspondence--Rowe, 1970-1971
  - Visiting Scientists Program--Reports, 1970-1971
  - Taxes, 1970-1971
  - Tax exempt letters, 1970-1972
  - Financial Statements--L. Guy Bennett, CPA, Includes Treasurer’s Report, 1971
  - Mailing lists changes, 1971
  - Social Security Tax Refund, 1971
  - Officers and Committees, 1971-1972
  - Appointment of Registered Agent--Correspondence--Rowe, 1971-1972
  - R. C. Berry--Correspondence, 1971-1972
  - F. F. Flint--Correspondence--President-elect; Turner, President, 1971-1972
  - Harshbarger--Correspondence, 1971-1972
  - P. C. Holt--Correspondence--W. S. Flory, 1971-1972
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Collegiate Chapters and Membership, 1971-1972
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Correspondence--Astronomy, Math, & Physics, Botany, Engineering, Geology, Medical Sciences, Microbiology, Science Teachers, and Space Science & Technology, 1971-1972
  - Agricultural Science Section--Correspondence--D. E. Bettry, 1971-1972
  - Annual Meeting--Schedule of Responsibilities, 1971-1972
  - Awards Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger and Turner, 1971-1972
  - Conservation & Natural Resources Committee--Correspondence--Hughes, 1971-1972
  - Executive Committee--Minutes--Council, 1971-1972
  - Fellow--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1971-1972
  - Finance Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1971-1972
  - Financial Structure--Correspondence--Ad Hoc Committee on Academy, 1971-1972
  - Finance Committee and Trustees--Correspondence and budget reports--Turner, 1971-1972
  - Long Range Planning Committee--Correspondence--Ulrich, 1971-1972
  - Nominations Committee--Correspondence, 1971-1972
  - Publications Committee--Correspondence--Flory and Dismal Swamp, 1971-1972
  - Science Museum of Virginia--Correspondence, reports, and brochures, 1971-1972
  - Directory of officers, council, etc., and original worksheets, 1971-1972
  - Financial Statements--L. Guy Bennett, 1972
  - Minutes of VAS and VJAS Meetings, 1972
  - Semi-Centennial Celebration, 1972
  - Mailing list changes, 1972
  - Social Security Tax Refund, 1972
  - IRS and State Taxes, 1972
  - Stanley Ragone--Correspondence--President, 1972-1973
  - Vera Remsburg--Notes--About VAS activities, 1972-1973
  - Miscellaneous Committees--Correspondence--Collegiate Chapters, Membership, and Place of meeting, 1972-1973
  - Miscellaneous Sections--Correspondence and reports--Biology, Botany, Chemistry, Microbiology, Science Teachers, Space Science and Technology, 1972-1973
  - Agricultural Science--Correspondence and minutes--U. F. Earp, 1972-1973
  - Annual Meeting and Local Arrangements--Schedule of Responsibilities, 1972-1973
  - Awards Committee--Correspondence--Whitehead and Remsburg, 1972-1973
  - Council, Academy Conference, and Assembly--Minutes, 1972-1973
- Box 13, 1972-1975 (Box 13)
  - Finance and Endowment Committee--Reports, 1972-1973
  - Flora Committee--Report, 1972-1973
  - I. D. Wilson--Correspondence-- "50 Years of VAS History," 1972-1973
  - Semi-Centennial Celebration--Correspondence and research--VAS History, 1972-1973
  - Semi-Centennial Committee--Correspondence--Harshbarger, 1972-1973
  - Files of Rodney Berry, 1972-1973
  - Financial Statements--L. Guy Bennett, 1973
  - Mailing list changes, 1973
  - Social Security Tax Refund, 1973
  - Taxes and Census Reports, 1973
  - Vera Remsburg--Correspondence, 1973-1974
  - E. L. Wisman--Correspondence--President-elect, 1973-1974
  - Annual Meeting--Schedule of Responsibilities, 1973-1974
  - Awards Committee--Correspondence, 1973-1974
  - Fellows--Correspondence--Remsburg, 1973-1974